magthemes.com 2017-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Recapture.io

### Privacy Policy Summary

At Recapture, we collect and manage data according to the following Privacy Policy (last update February 2, 2017).

#### **TL;DR**

  * **Your data is yours & you can change or delete it at any time.**
  * We never share any information about your campaigns, carts or customers, with anyone unless you explicitly allow us to.
  * To provide better service, we share some statistical data and some personal information with third parties.
  * We comply with laws from EU-US Privacy Shield and for EU customers, they supercede US laws
  * You’re welcome to use content blocking software (e.g. to remove analytics tags); however be aware that this may interfere with our ability to track errors and performance issues that affect your account.
  * We encrypt backups, don’t store credit card numbers on our servers and generally make sure your data is safe.
  * When legally required, or when we suspect fraud, we may share data with law enforcement.
  * If you have questions, write to [privacy@recapture.io](mailto:privacy@Recapture.io).

### Privacy Policy: The Boring Details

By using Recapture.io (the “Website”) and/or a Recapture account (the “Service”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. Recapture is designed and operated by Skyline Consulting Co d/b/a Recapture.io (“Recapture”). Please read the Terms of Service in their entirety, and refer to those for definitions and contacts.

#### Data Collected

We collect anonymous data from every visitor of the Website to monitor traffic and fix bugs. For example, we collect information like web requests, the data sent in response to such requests, the Internet Protocol address, the browser type, the browser language, and a timestamp for the request.

For the Service, we ask you to register an account, log in and provide certain information (such as names and email addresses of your team members, your company name and address and your credit card information) in order to be able to store your cart data and emails, as well as periodically automatically bill you & charge your card (credit card numbers are never stored on Recapture servers, but are securely transmitted and stored with our payment provider).

We use cookies to store session information for your convenience. Cookies must be enabled to use the Website and the Service.

In order to take advantage of certain features of the Service, you may also choose to provide us with other personal information, such as your picture, but your decision to utilize these features and provide such data will always be voluntary.

#### Use of the Data

We only use your personal information to provide you with the Service to communicate with you about the Service or the Website.

With respect to any data you may choose to enter or upload to Recapture, we take the privacy and confidentiality of this data seriously. Your data (in the Service) is specifically not shared between accounts or with the public. We employ industry standard techniques to protect against unauthorized access of data that we store, including personal information. All off-site backups of your data are securely encrypted.

Please note that if you choose to share data (like sharing invoices with your clients), we are not responsible for any violation of privacy law you may be liable for.

We do not share personal information you have provided to us without your consent, unless:

  * doing so is appropriate to carry out a user’s request;
  * we believe it’s necessary in order to provide the highest quality of service;
  * we believe it’s needed to enforce our Terms of Service, or that is legally required;
  * we believe it’s needed to detect, prevent or address fraud, security or technical issues;
  * otherwise protect our property, legal rights, or that of others.

Recapture is operated from the United States. Customers from the European Union are covered under the EU-US Privacy Shield Act of 2016. If you are visiting the Website from outside the U.S. or the E.U., you agree to any processing of any personal information you provide us according to U.S. policy.

Recapture may contact you by email. For example, Recapture may send you promotional emails relating to Recapture or communicate with you about your use of the Recapture Website and Service. If you do not want to receive email from Recapture, please opt out of receiving emails at the bottom of any Recapture email. Please note that for some emails (for example billing issues), there’s no option to opt-out.

#### Support for EU-US Privacy Shield

##### EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework

Recapture is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). Recapture complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Recapture has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over Recapture’s compliance with the Privacy Shield.

##### EU-US Privacy Complaints

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield, Recapture commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Dave Rodenbaugh at Recapture at [privacy@recapture.com](mailto:privacy@recapture.com), or by mail at 

Skyline Consulting Co d/b/a Recapture.io  
10558 Lieter Pl  
Lone Tree, CO 80124  
United States

We will thoroughly investigate the matter internally and make every effort to attempt to resolve the issue quickly.

Recapture has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles to BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your complaint, please contact or visit the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD at <https://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/> for more information and to file a complaint. The services of BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD are provided at no cost to you.

Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel. For more information please see <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction>.

#### Sharing of Data

We don’t share your personal information with third parties except as listed below. Only aggregated, statistical data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Recapture Website and Service.

For client-side analytics and tracking beacons, you’re welcome to use content blocking software; just be aware that this may influence our ability to identify errors and performance problems in your account. We can’t guarantee that Recapture will work as intended when browser extensions alter the HTML, CSS or JavaScript code we transmit (however, we don’t take any active steps to prevent you from using extensions, including content blockers).

We currently use Customer.io (in-app customer support), HelpScout (email customer support), Google Analytics, and Drip (email marketing). We listed below what data these third parties extract exactly. Feel free to check out their own Privacy Policies to find out more.

  * Customer.io: your name, email and aggregated account statistics
  * HelpScout: your name, email and aggregated account statistics
  * Google Analytics: no personally identifiable data is shared
  * Drip: your name, email and aggregated account statistics

Additionally, Recapture uses third party vendors that provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage and other technology required to run the Website and the Service. While Recapture owns the rights to the Recapture Website and Service, you retain all rights to the data you enter into Recapture.

In other to provide the Service, we also share data with services that help us track errors and bugs, keep backups of log files and identify performance issues.

We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our “Agents”). We may need to share personal information with our Agents in order to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents.

If Recapture is acquired or merged with an other company, or Recapture sells the Recapture Website and Service to an other company, or if Recapture goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information may be transferred to a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Recapture or its assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

#### Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make any significant changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Website or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

#### Questions

Should you have any question or concern, please email [privacy@Recapture.io](mailto:privacy@recapture.io), or write to:

Skyline Consulting Co d/b/a Recapture.io  
10558 Lieter Pl  
Lone Tree, CO 80124  
United States

#### Change Log

  * _Version 1.1, February 2, 2017._ Transferred ownership to Skyline Consulting, added clause for EU-US Privacy Shield support.
  * _Version 1.0, December 15, 2015._ Initial release.
